[{"id":375,"question":"Once a table has been created in MySQL, its structure cannot be altered","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":405,"question":"The program called MySQL is","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"There Isn't A Program Just Called Mysql","answer_b":"A Client Program That Lets You Send SQL Commands To The Database Engine","answer_c":"The Database Engine","answer_d":"A Wrapper Through Which Java Clients Must Connect To The Databases  The Database Engine","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":369,"question":"Which of the following is a valid aggregate function","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CURDATE()","answer_b":"COUNT","answer_c":"AVERAGE","answer_d":"MAXIMUM","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":357,"question":"Which of the following scripts will run successfully","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Users statistics SELECT customer name FROM customers;","answer_b":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers WHERE cat_id = 12 ORDER BY cat_id;","answer_c":"SELECT FROM `customers` 'customer name';","answer_d":"SELECT `customer name` FROM customers ORDER BY zone WHERE cat_id = 12;","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":215,"question":"Which command is used to modify column names or table structure?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"MODIFY","answer_b":"ADD","answer_c":"CHANGE","answer_d":"ALTER","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":379,"question":"What will be the output of the query SELECT * FROM `members` LIMIT 1, 2;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will generate an error","answer_b":"the query will return all records from the members table","answer_c":"the query will return the first 2 records","answer_d":"the query will return skip the first record then return the following 2 records only","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":397,"question":"Commands passed to the MySQL daemon are written in","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"English","answer_b":"The Structured Query Language","answer_c":"Your Choice From Perl, PHP, Java Or Some Other Languages","answer_d":"Swedish","answer_e":"Binary","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":329,"question":"How can you change table sctructure after it was created?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"CHANGE TABLE","answer_b":"MODIFY TABLE","answer_c":"ALTER TABLE","answer_d":"UPDATE TABLE","answer_e":"It's not possible to change the structure","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":212,"question":"Which operator is not included in the data manipulation language (DML)?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"UPDATE","answer_b":"DELETE","answer_c":"CREATE","answer_d":"SELECT","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":227,"question":"Which SQL statement is used to extract data from the database?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT","answer_b":"ACCESS","answer_c":"OPEN","answer_d":"GET","answer_e":"ACQUIRE","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Easy"}]